Guide to the Records of The Weiss & Klau Co. 1892-1988 (Bulk 1922-1968) MS 687
New-York Historical Society
Weiss & Klau Co. Records
1890-1988 (Bulk 1922-1968)
New-York Historical Society
MS 687
6.5 Linear feet (16 Boxes)
Corporate, financial, legal, personnel, and real estate records of The Weiss & Klau Co., a distributor of oilcloth, plastic-coated fabrics, window shades, and related products. The collection also includes the records of a subsidiary, Standard Coated Products, Inc., a manufacturer of these products. Photographs and memorabilia of company social functions are also present, as is some personal correspondence.
Provenance
Donation, 2003.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Certain materials in Series I and IV are restricted for 75 years. See the Scope and Content Notes for details.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. (Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.)
Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. Please contact manuscripts@nyhistory.org prior to your research visit to coordinate access. Keep in mind that it will take between two (2) and five (5) business days for collections to arrive, and you should plan your research accordingly.
Historical Note
Missing Title
1887 Ignatz Weiss, Nathan Klau and Samuel Klau found the firm Weiss & Klau Brothers, for the purpose of selling and distributing table oil cloth and window shades.
1892 Weiss & Klau Brothers moves to 203 Canal Street.
1895 Samuel Klau dies.
1896 Company changes its name to Weiss & Klau.
1897 Company expands to 205, 207, 209, and 211 Canal Street.
1898 Company changes name to The Weiss & Klau Co. and is incorporated in New York State.
1911 The Weiss & Klau Co. moves to 462-468 Broadway. David Klau, son of Nathan Klau, joins company as office boy.
1922 The Weiss & Klau Co. purchases Napaul Corporation.
1937 The Weiss & Klau Co. buys bonds of Standard Textile Products, Inc., their main supplier of oil cloth and other products, in order to allow the purchase of Standard Textile by Interchemical Corporation. Fiftieth anniversary of founding of Weiss & Klau; Golden Jubilee celebrated.
1938 Nathan Klau dies; David Klau becomes president of company.
1946 Quarter-Century Club created. The club consisted of employees who had worked for Weiss & Klau for twenty-five years or more.
1953 The Weiss & Klau Co. purchases Standard Coated Products, Inc., (formerly Standard Textile Products, Inc.) manufacturer of textiles and Weiss & Klau's chief supplier.
1961 David Klau dies. Ira Oppenheimer (grandson of Nathan Klau and nephew of David Klau) becomes President.
1962 Seventy-fifth anniversary of founding of company; Diamond Jubilee celebrated.
1966 On January 27, part of the fifth floor of building at 462 Broadway collapses. Several employees are injured. In February, the plastic stock window shade business is sold to Breneman, Inc. In March, the plastic film and tile business is sold to Clopay Corporation.
1968 Standard Coated Products, Inc. is sold to American Cyanamid. The Weiss & Klau Co. changes name to K Liquidating Company and ceases operation.
Scope and Content Note
The records of The Weiss & Klau Co. consist primarily of corporate, financial, legal, personnel, and real estate records. The company, along with its subsidiaries, including Standard Coated Products, Inc., Airex Venetian Blind Co., and 462 Broadway Corporation, was engaged in the manufacture, sale, and distribution, of oilcloth, window shades, plastic coated fabrics and tiles, venetian blinds and related products. Many of the records deal with the dissolution and sale of the company following the partial collapse of the Weiss & Klau offices at 462 Broadway in 1966. The collection also contains materials related to various social functions held by the company. There are numerous photographs of annual dinners and company outings. In addition, there is material relating the The Quarter-Century Club, an employee social organization which held annual meetings until 1988.
The collection supports research in New York City business administrative history from the late nineteenth through the mid-twentieth century. In addition, materials relating to employee relations and social functions provide insight into organizational culture and the environment of the work place in this time period.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into the following eight series:
Missing Title
Series I. Corporate Documents, 1896-1968, n.d.
Series II. Financial Documents, 1902-1969
Series III. Real Estate Documents, 1912-1981
Series IV. Personnel Documents, 1936-1981
Series V. Standard Coated Products, Inc., 1922-1971, n.d.
Series VI. Sale and Liquidation, 1890-1973
Series VII. Social Functions, 1915-1988, n.d.
Series VIII. Scrapbooks, Photographs, and Ephemera, 1896-1966, n.d.
The materials are arranged chronologically within each series, unless otherwise noted.
Separated Material
A metal plaque commemorating the seventy-fifth anniversary of The Weiss & Klau Co. is owned by The New-York Historical Society Museum.
Ledgers (account books).; Legal documents.; Minutes (administrative records); Newsletters.; Correspondence.; Notes (documents).; Pamphlets.; Contracts.; Deeds.; Scrapbooks.; Certificates.; Photographs.; Wills.; Stock certificates.; Souvenir programs; Clippings (information artifacts); Building plans.; Account books.; Work environment; Sales management; Pension trusts.; Organizational behavior.; Oilcloth industry; Liquidation; Industrial relations; Consolidation and merger of corporations; Collapse of Buildings; Coated Fabrics industry.; Ephemera.; Financial records.; Leases; Airex Venetian Blind Co.; American Cyanamid Company; Breneman, Inc.; Clopay Corporation; DeSoto Chemical Coatings; Guaranty Trust Company of New York; Hanover Bank (New York, N.Y.); Interchemical Corporation; Klau (Family); Klau, David, -1961; Klau, Nathan, -1938; Napaul Corporation; New York Trust Company; Oppenheimer, Ira L., -2004; Ru-Son Products, Inc.; Standard Textile Products Company; The Weiss & Klau Co.; Weiss & Klau Brothers; 462 Broadway Corporation (New York, N.Y.)
- Series I: Corporate Documents, 1896-1968
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains materials related to The Weiss & Klau Co.'s status as a corporation, including board minutes, resolutions, stock certificate books, and other materials. Also included are the general correspondence of the company, materials related to trademarks, and records retention schedules.
  Materials related to the distribution of Weiss & Klau stock in Box 2, Folder 3 are restricted until 2043, 75 years from the date of their creation.
  - Corporate Documents and Agreements, 1896-1908 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board Minutes, 1898-1910 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board Minutes, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board Minutes, 1968 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Resolution, 1943 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1898-1947 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
  - Corporate and Financial Summaries--All Companies, 1923-1968 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stock Certificate Book, 1947-1959 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stock Certificate Book, 1959-1968 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bond Registers, 1963 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
  - Stock Valuation, 1962 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
  - Distribution of W & K Stock (RESTRICTED), 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
  - Redemption of W & K Stock, 1965 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
  - SANITAS Trademark, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
  - Certificates of Incorporation and Merger--Napaul Corporation (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
  - Napaul Corporation--By-Laws, Certificate of Merger, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
  - Summons, 1968 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
  - Records Retention Schedule, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 9)
  - List of Document Locations, n.d. (Offsite-box 2, Folder 10)
- Series II: Financial Documents, 1902-1969
  This series contains financial documents, including inventory records, balance sheets, account books, investment reports, sales figures, and tax returns of The Weiss & Klau Co., its related companies, and its principal investors.
  - Inventory Record, 1903-1914 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 11)
  - Inventory, 1925 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 12)
  - Check and Receipt, 1902-1919 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
  - Balance Sheet, 1922 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
  - Balance Sheet, 1955-1965 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
  - Consolidation of Balance Sheets and Income Accounts, 1955-1965 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 16)
  - Account Book, 1966 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 17)
  - Account Book, 1967 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
  - Account Book, 1968 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
  - Profit and Loss Accounts, 1956-1969 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
  - Report on Financial Statements, 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
  - Projections, 1966 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
  - Projected Statements of Income, 1966 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records, 1936-1954 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
  - Financial Records, 1956-1965 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records, 1958-1964 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9)
  - Financial Records, 1965 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 10)
  - Financial Records, 1966 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11)
  - Financial Records, 1967 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 12)
  - Consolidated Net Assets of All Companies, 1948-1963 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
  - Assets of Companies and Persons, 1955-1960 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
  - Schedule of Investments, 1922-1923 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
  - Investments, 1967 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
  - FAB Department Records, 1951-1963 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sales Binder, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
  - Salesmanship Manual, 1946 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
  - Capital Stock Tax Return, 1942-1945 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
  - Tax Estimates, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9)
  - Tax Materials, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 10)
  - Audits, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 11)
- Series III: Real Estate Documents, 1912-1981
  The Weiss & Klau Co. moved into its home at 462-468 Broadway in 1911. This series contains legal and real estate documents relating to the purchase (and sale) of the building, lease agreements, repairs and construction work. This series also contains information relating to the partial collapse of the building in 1966. There are clippings from several New York City papers; correspondence with employees, attorneys, and actuaries; building violations; and materials relating to insurance and liability claims.
  - Real Estate Documents, 1912-1922 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
  - Real Estate Documents, 1939-1942 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 13)
  - Real Estate Documents, 1943 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 14)
  - Real Estate Documents, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 15)
  - Real Estate Documents, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 16)
  - Real Estate Documents, 1949-1958 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Documents, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
  - Annual Vault Charge, 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
  - Notes, Drawings Re: Building Collapse, 1966 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sale of Building--Correspondence, Notes, Clippings, 1966, 1981 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
  - Building Violations, 1966 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lists of Injured Employees, 1966 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
  - Insurance Claims, Correspondence, Notes, 1966 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lawsuit--Legal Documents, Correspondence, Notes, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings--Building Collapse, 1966 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings--Sale of Business, 1966 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 11)
  - Registration of Insured Boiler, 1968 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 12)
- Series IV: Personnel Documents, 1936-1981
  This series contains the personnel records of Weiss & Klau employees, as well as extensive materials relating to the pension plan created for employees following the building collapse in 1966.
  The personnel records contained in Box 5, Folders 13 and 14, are restricted until 2042, 75 years from the last date of their creation.
  - Personnel Records (RESTRICTED), 1939-1967 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 13)
  - Personnel Records (RESTRICTED), 1939-1967 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 14)
  - Permit to Pay Employees by Check, 1936, 1963 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
  - Attendance Record, 1936 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
  - Calculation of Bonuses, 1946 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Compensation Plan, 1948 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
  - Executive Compensation, 1955-1968 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
  - Profit-Sharing Plan, 1958-1965 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
  - Harry A. Propp--Correspondence, Notes, 1944-1966, n.d. (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
  - Watchmen--Schedules, Notes, 1966 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sales and Executive Payroll, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 9)
  - Employment of Ira L. Oppenheimer, 1962 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 10)
  - Termination of Ira L. Oppenheimer, 1966 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 11)
  - Terminations--Letters and Notes, 1966 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pension and Emplopyee Benefits Plans, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 13)
  - Pension Plan--Deferred Compensation Agreements, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 14)
  - Pension Plan--Notes, Statistical Data, 1963-1966 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 15)
  - Group Pension Contract, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 16)
  - Pension Plan--Request for Determination, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 17)
  - Request for Determination, 1968 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pension Plan--Notes, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pension Plan--Correspondence with Employees, 1966 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 3)
  - Pension Plan--Correspondence with Attorneys and Actuaries, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pension Plan--Correspondence with Attorneys and Actuaries, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
  - Informal Pension Plan, 1968 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
  - Pension Plan--Correspondence re: Disputed Claim, 1970 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pension Plan--Periodic Payment File Listing, 1981 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 8)
- Series V: Standard Coated Products, 1922-1971, n.d.
  Standard Coated Products, Inc. (known until 1937 as Standard Textile Products, Inc.) was Weiss & Klau's largest supplier of oilcloth and other textile products. Standard Coated was purchased by Weiss & Klau from Interchemical Corporation in 1953. This series contains correspondence, financial records, marketing reports, legal documents, clippings, and other materials relating to Standard Coated dating from both before and after its acquisition by Weiss & Klau.
  - Standard Textile Products--Corporate Documents, Correspondence, 1922-1934 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 9)
  - Standard Textile Products--Clippings, 1925-1937 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 10)
  - Standard Textile (Coated) Products--Corporate Documents, Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 11)
  - Standard Coated Products--Corporate Documents, Correspondence, 1938-1944 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 12)
  - Agreement with Interchemical Corp., 1953 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1)
  - Agreement with Interchemical Corp., 1953 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 2)
  - Standard Coated Products--Corporate and Financial Documents, Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 3)
  - Standard Coated Products--Corporate and Financial Documents, Correspondence, 1955, n.d. (Offsite-box 8, Folder 4)
  - Loan Documents by Standard Coated Products and Weiss & Klau with New York Trust Company, 1955 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 5)
  - Loan Documents by Standard Coated Products and Weiss & Klau with New York Trust Company, 1955 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
  - Loan Documents by Standard Coated Products and Weiss & Klau with Guaranty Trust Company, 1955 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 7)
  - Loan Documents by Standard Coated Products and Weiss & Klau with Guaranty Trust Company and New York Trust Company, 1955 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 8)
  - Loan Documents by Standard Coated Products and Weiss & Klau with Hanover Bank and Renewal with Guaranty Trust Company, 1956 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 9)
  - Standard Coated Products--Corporate and Financial Documents, Notes, 1956-1971, n.d. (Offsite-box 8, Folder 10)
  - Appraisal of Standard Coated Products, 1958 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 11)
  - Standard Coated Products--Financial Statements, 1954-1964 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 12)
  - Standard Coated Products--Financial Records, 1958-1960 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
  - Standard Coated Products--Financial Records, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
  - Standard Coated Products--Financial Records, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
  - Interchemical Review, 1949 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
  - Market Outlook for Oilcloth, 1949 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 5)
  - Outlook for Coated Products Division, Interchemical Corp., 1952 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 6)
  - Studies--Combination of Standard Coated Products and Weiss & Klau, 1966 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 7)
- Series VI: Sale and Liquidation, 1890-1973
  Following the collapse of 462 Broadway, portions of The Weiss & Klau Co. were sold to different companies. This series contains correspondence, notes, legal, and financial documents relating to the purchase of the plastic stock window shade business by Breneman, Inc. in February 1966, the plastic film and tile business by Clopay Corporation in March 1966, and the manufacturing business of Standard Coated Products, Inc. by American Cyanamid Corporation in 1968. It also contains materials relating to the final liquidation of stock and assets of The Weiss & Klau Co. In addition, correspondence, notes, and other materials relating to unsuccessful bids to purchase Weiss & Klau, both before and after the building collapse are found here. In particular, there is a considerable amount of information relating to a possible merger with DeSoto Chemical Coatings. Finally, this series contains Dun & Bradstreet Reports on Weiss & Klau and their competitors.
  - Dun & Bradstreet Reports, 1890-1948 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 8)
  - Offers to Purchase Business--Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 9)
  - Offers to Purchase Business--Notes, Annual Reports, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Purchase of Ru-Son Products, 1963 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 11)
  - Corporate Research Materials--DeSoto Chemical Coatings, 1957-1966 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Notes--DeSoto Chemical Coatings, 1957-1966 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
  - Breneman, Inc., 1966-1973 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
  - Breneman, Clopay, Newell, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
  - Clopay Corporation, 1956-1968 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 5)
  - Sale of Assets to Clopay Corporation, 1966 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sale of Industrial Fabrics Division, 1966 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sale of Industrial Fabrics Division, 1966 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 8)
  - Sale of Industrial Fabrics Division, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 9)
  - Ameican Cyanamid--Annual Reports, Advertising, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 10)
  - American Cyanamid--Correspondence, Notes, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
  - Sale of Assets to American Cyanamid Company, 1968 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2)
  - Sale to American Cyanamid--Marked Copies of Agreement, 1968 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
  - 462 Broadway Corp.--Board Minutes, Resolution, 1966 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4)
  - Liquidation of 462 Broadway Corp., 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 5)
  - Liquidation, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
  - Corporate Dissolution, 1968 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
  - Liquidation, 1968 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
  - Liquidation, 1969 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
  - Liquidation, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
  - Notes re: Liquidation, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
  - Outline of Will of David Klau, 1957 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
- Series VII: Social Functions and Activities, 1915-1988
  The Weiss & Klau Co. regularly hosted parties and other events for its employees. This series contains programs from dinners, as well as materials relating to large parties held in honor of the fiftieth and seventy-fifth anniversaries of the company. In addition, there are company newsletters, many of which contain personal information about employees, such as wedding, birth, and death announcements, work-related news, jokes, and cartoons. This series also contains materials relating to two employee social organizations, The Quarter-Century Club and The Old Bunch. Finally, this series contains the personal correspondence of Ira L. Oppenheimer, its last president, with employees, friends, and associates.
  - Dance Programs, 1915-1939 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary--Speeches, Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 7)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary--Mailing List, Broadside, 1936 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 8)
  - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary--Budget, Invoices, Notes, 1962 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 9)
  - Employee Newsletter, 1928-1970 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 10)
  - Quarter-Century Club--Membership Lists, 1955-1982 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 11)
  - Quarter-Century Club--Announcements, 1968-1971, n.d. (Offsite-box 12, Folder 12)
  - Quarter-Century Club--Correspondence, Notes, 1968-1982 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 13)
  - Quarter-Century Club--Correspondence, Notes, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Old Bunch, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
  - Speeches, 1958-1961, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
  - Clipping, 1961 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence of Ira L. Oppenheimer, 1961-1971 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
- Series VII: Scrapbooks, Photographs, and Ephemera, 1896-1966, n.d.
  This series consists primarily of two scrapbooks containing photographs, newsletters, newspaper clippings, certificates, advertisements, correspondence, cartoons, and other materials pertaining to The Weiss & Klau Co., its employees, its related businesses, and the Klau family. Some of these materials appear elsewhere in the collection. Many of the materials date from the early twentieth century. There are a number of group photographs taken at company dinners. Individuals have been identified in several of these photographs. One scrapbook containing oversized materials has been disbound, and the contents have been arranged in folders. The other scrapbook remains in its original condition. In addition, this series contains business-related ephemera, such as announcements and business cards, additional photographs, and a wooden printing block used by the firm of Weiss & Klau Brothers.
  - Announcements, 1896, 1966 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6)
  - Business Cards, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 13, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 14, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Offsite-box 15)
  - Photographs (Copies), 1924-1926 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Slides, n.d. (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)